#### Contact

rn35@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aisha-mba-msn-rn-cmsrn-lnc-416a8ba9 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Management Microsoft Word

#### Certifications

Certified Medical Surgical Nurse

# Aisha MBA,MSN,RN,CMSRN,LNC

Nurse Manager at Texas Health Resources Red Oak, Texas

# Summary

I am a goal-oriented and highly talented Registered Nurse with 15 fulfilling years of progressive clinical background experience in acute care medical-surgical settings. I have excellent communication and leadership skills. I demonstrate strong clinical skills with a proven record to go above and beyond to advocate for patient needs and safety.

My ultimate goal is to seek a position that will allow me the opportunity to use my knowledge and experience to lead and manage others in providing quality care to patients.

# Experience

Texas Health Resources

Nurse Manager

November 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Texas Health Arlington Memorial Hospital Resource Nurse Supervisor April 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months)

UnitedHealth Group Clinical Nurse Manager September 2011 - January 2014 (2 years 5 months)

Arlington Memorial Hospital
Resource/Admission Discharge Nurse
May 2007 - September 2011 (4 years 5 months)

Intelistaff Healthcare
Travel RN
May 2006 - June 2007 (1 year 2 months)

## Medical Center of Arlington Staff RN January 2005 - May 2007 (2 years 5 months)

Lafayette General Health LPN September 2002 - September 2003 (1 year 1 month)

## Education

Loyola University New Orleans

Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing Administration · (2018)

Texas Woman's University

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Business Administration and

Management, General · (2009 - 2011)

McNeese State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2002 - 2004)

University of Houston Legal Nurse Consulting